Neufeld, Maurice Papers /3007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II. XEROX FILES
  - Contracts - Grievances, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 40-54)
    Memo from W. B. Winstanley to Asher re hourly wage increase recommendaton [1/24/66], syllabus of collective bargaining course taught to 18 members of bargaining committee of Rochester ACWU [2/2/66], memo from Asher to Wilson re arrangements and goals of 1966 wage negotiations (includes hand-written note by MFN) [2/7/66], memo from Wigg re Union's request to reopen contract negotiations and discuss a general wage increase (includes charts detailing results of Company's local wage survey) [2/14/66], minutes of 1966 wage negotiation meeting [2/18/66], notes of David Riordan, spokesman of Company negotiating team, re composition of Company team, summary of positions on both sides re wage increase, minutes of wage negotiation meetings [2/24-3/24/66], minutes of IUOE contract negotiation meetings [3/9/66], memo from A.G. Murray re the progress of Apprentice Program negotiations (includes copy of Tool and Die Maker Apprenticeship Contract) [5/12/66], minutes of meetings discussing details of IUOE contract [5/13/66], minutes of meeting discussing re-draft of IUOE contract [6/22/66], summary of non-economic changes in Xerox-ACWU labor agreement (includes notes by MFN) [11/66], Xerox newsletter with article re overtime policy for exempt salaried employees [12/1/66], minutes of meetings held between Company and Union to negotiate a contract for employees at Oak Brook, IL plant (includes first draft of contract) [3/25/66-4/22/66], minutes of Company-Union contract negotiation meetings for Irvine, CA plant [7/7/66-7/19/66], minutes of meetings re grievances and employee discipline.
  - Contracts, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 1-8)
    Memo from Asher to C.P. McColough re alternation compositions of Company Negotiation Committee for 1967 contract talks [12/16/66], minutes of Company-Union contract negotiation meetings [held from 1/20/67 to 3/18/67], copy of 1967 labor agreement (with MFN notes) [3/18/67], addenda to contract (including summaries of Union demands and Company responses), analyses of Union demands (with MFN notes) [1,2,3/67], minutes of Negotiating Committee meeting discussing Union ratification vote [3/29/67], minutes of meetings addressing unresolved issues of contract negotiations between Company and ACWU for Oakville, Ontario plant [12/20/67].
  - Contracts - Grievances, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 9-29)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings held at Rochester and Chicago plants re grievances, employee discipline, and routine business, copies of employee grievance reports
  - Contracts, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 30-39)
    List of Union organization at Xerox plants [11/67], minutes of contract negotiations held between management and Union of regional plants, copies of labor agreements (regional centers include Atlanta, Blauvelt (NY), Dallas, Des Plaines, Oak Brook, Rockleigh (NJ), St. Louis, San Francisco, Washington DC, and IUOE at Rochester).
  - BPSD (Business Products and Systems Division Manufacturing) - Minutes, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re a supplemental compensation plan for Assembly employees of the BP&SD at Rochester (includes copy of plan) [2/9/68], minutes of meetings re grievances, discipline and routine business
  - CAD (Corporate Administration Division) -Grievances and Reports, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    Grievances and reports re employees in CAD.
  - CAD - Minutes, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    Minutes of annual Company-Union meeting of model shops personnel [l/11/68], and meetings re grievances, International Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE) joint apprenticeship program [5/8/68], and routine business.
  - Columbus - Grievances and Reports, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    Minutes of meeting with International Brotherhood of Bookbinders in Columbus, Ohio [2/7/68].
  - Corporate Industrial Relations, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    Memo from Brayer to Asher re monthly Industrial Relations meeting with MFN [1/23/68], Company statements re various grievances heard at arbitration, opinions and awards of arbiters in these matters [6/21/68].
  - Discipline, Suspension, Discharge, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 45-46)
    Minutes of routine disciplinary meetings
  - Irvine - Grievances and Reports, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 47-49)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re routine grievance reports at Irvine (CA) plant.
  - ISD (Information Systems Division) - Reports, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 50-58)
    Grievance reports from ISD
  - ISD - Minutes, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Memo from J. P. Barr re April 24 ISD Company-Union meeting [5-13-68].
  - MA (Manufacturing Dept., Assembly Section) -Grievances and Reports - I, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 2-11)
    Grievance reports from Assembly Section.
  - MA - Grievances and Reports - II, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 12-18)
    Grievance reports from Assembly Section
  - MF (Manufacturing Dept., Fabrication Section) -Grievances and Reports - I, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 19-27)
    Grievance reports from Fabrication Section.
  - MF - Grievances and Reports - II, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 28-31)
    Grievance reports from Fabrication Section
  - MF - Minutes, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    Minutes of meetings reviewing new programs in Fabrication Section
  - MM (Manufacturing Dept., Materials Section) -Reports, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 33-40)
    Grievance reports from Materials Manufacturing.
  - MMS (Manufacturing Dept., Models Shop) - Grievances and Reports, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    Grievance reports from Models Shop
  - Oak Brook - Grievances and Reports, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 42-43)
    Minutes of meetings re grievances and employee discipline at Oak Brook plant
  - Paper (Photo Division) - Grievances and Reports, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    Grievance reports from Photo Division
  - PMS(X) (Process Manufacturing Section) -Grievances, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 45-47)
    Grievance reports from PMS, X seniority unit.
  - PMS(X) - Minutes, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    Minutes of meetings re routine business in PMS, X seniority unit
  - R (Rockleigh) -Reports, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 49-51)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re grievances, discipline, and routine business at Rockleigh (NJ) plant.
  - R&AED - Minutes, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 52)
    Minutes of Company-Union meeting re disciplinary action in Research and Advanced Engineering Development.
  - Arbitration, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 53-54)
    Opinions and awards of arbiters, briefs and opening statements of Company
  - BPSD - MFG (Manufacturing Dept.) - Minutes, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 55)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re seniority and routine business
  - C (Cleaners Division) - Grievances and Reports, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 56)
    Grievance reports from Cleaners Division
  - Contracts, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 57)
    Copy of labor agreement between Cheshire Inc., a Xerox company (Mundelein, ID, and the International Association of Machinists and Aero-Space Workers [1/31/69].
  - Discipline, Suspension, Discharge, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 58-60)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re disciplinary proceedings
  - Irvine - Grievances and Reports, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 61-64)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re overtime equalization and other routine matters
  - ISD - Grievances and Reports, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 65-69)
    Grievance reports from ISD.
  - ISD - Minutes, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 70)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re annual review [l/16/69], and routine business.
  - MA - Grievances and Reports - I, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 1-7)
  - MA - Grievances and Reports - II, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 8-12)
    Further grievance reports from Assembly Section
  - MF - Grievances and Reports - I, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 13-19)
  - MF - Grievances and Reports - II, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 20-26)
    Further grievance reports from Fabrication Section
  - MM - Grievances and Reports, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 27-32)
    Grievance reports from Materials Manufacturing Section.
  - MM - Minutes, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    Minutes of meetings re Union concerns that regional Company plants were manufacturing machines at the expense of Rochester plants, and Company's assurance that products engineered at Webster (NY) would remain and be built in the Rochester are [7/12/69].
  - MMS - Grievances and Reports, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    Grievance reports from Model Shops.
  - Oak Brook - Grievances and Reports, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    Minutes of Company-Union meeting re grievances and discipline at Oak Brook plant
  - Paper - Grievances and Reports, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - PMS(X) - Grievances, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 37-38)
    Grievance reports from Process Manufacturing Section, X seniority unit
  - PMS(X) - Minutes, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re routine business in PMS, X seniority unit.
  - S (Maintenance and Building Services) - Grievances and Reports, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    Grievance reports from Building Services.
  - S - Minutes, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    Minutes of Company-Union meeting re ACWA Apprenticeship [12/15/69].
  - Arbitration, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 42-46)
    Opinions and awards of arbiters for 1970 arbitration hearings
  - BPG (Business Products Group) - Contracts, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 47-67)
    Outline of Company plans for 1970 contract negotiations [9/30/69], Union proposals for contract changes (with Company analysis) [1/12/70], Company proposals [1/21/70], minutes of Company-Union contract negotiation meetings (includes index) [meetings held from 1/12/70 to 3/21/70], copy of report of agreements reached over Union and Company demands, memo of understanding between Union and Company (2 copies, second includes index; with MFN notes) [5/21/703, copy of labor agreement (with MFN notes) [6/11/70], memo from Asher re follow-up to 1970 labor agreement [6/15/70], minutes of contract negotiation meetings held by Xerox Corp. and IUOE [held from 5/27/70 to 6/26/70], final copies of ACWA contract for 1970-1973.
  - C - Grievances and Reports, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Grievances and Reports for Cleaners Section.
  - CPD - Grievances and Reports, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 2-6)
    Grievances and Reports for Communication Products Divison (successor to Information Systems Division).
  - Discipline, Suspension, Discharge, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 7-13)
    Minutes of Company-Union proceedings re disciplinary action
  - Irvine - Contracts, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 14-16)
    Minutes of contract negotiation meetings held at Irvine plant [held from 7/9/70 to 8/22/70].
  - Irvine - Grievances and Reports, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 17-18)
    Minutes of Union-Company meetings re routine business
  - MA - Grievances and Reports, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 19-25)
  - MF - Grievances and Reports, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 26-32)
  - MF - Minutes, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    Minutes of Company-Union and department meetings re routine business of Fabrication Section.
  - MM - Grievances and Reports, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 34-35)
  - MMS - Grievances and Reports, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    Grievance reports from Model Shop Section.
  - Oak Brook - Contracts, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 37-38)
    Proposed contract changes by Union and Company, minutes of contract negotiation meetings held at Oak Brook plant [held from 4/13/70 to 5/9/70].
  - Paper - Grievances and Reports, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - PMS(X) - Grievances, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    Grievance reports from Process Manufacturing Section.
  - San Francisco - Contracts, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    Minutes of contract negotiation meetings held at San Francisco plant [held from 5/12/70 to 5/14/70].
  - Service and Maintenance - Grievances and Reports, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    Grievance reports from Maintenance Section
  - Service - Minutes, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    Minutes if meetings re routing business in Maintenance Section
  - Arbitration, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 44-52)
    Opinions and awards of arbiter, company briefs and evidence
  - BPG - MFG - Minutes, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    Company-Union meetings re Company subcontracting and routine business.
  - Cleaners - Grievances and Reports, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    Grievance reports from Cleaners Section
  - Discipline, Suspension, Discharge, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 55-61)
  - Irvine - Grievances and Reports, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 62-63)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re routine business
  - MA - Grievances and Reports - I, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 64-69)
  - MA - Grievances and Reports - II, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 70-74)
  - MC (Corporate Trucking) - Grievances and Reports, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
    Grievance reports from Corporate Trucking
  - MD (Distribution) - Grievances and Reports, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    Grievance reports from Distribution
  - MF - Grievances and Reports, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 4-6)
  - MH (Henrietta) - Grievances and Reports, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 7-13)
    Grievance reports from Henrietta Plant
  - MMS - Grievances and Reports, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - P (Photo) - Grievances and Reports, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - S - Grievances and Reports, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    Grievance reports from Service and Maintenance Section.
  - X - Grievances and Reports, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    Grievance reports from X seniority unit.
  - Arbitration, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    Arbitration opinions and awards, Company briefs and Union statements
  - Blauvelt - Contracts, 1970-1973 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    Labor agreement between Company and Union for Blauvelt Distribution Center [11/2/70].
  - BPG - Contract, 1970-1973 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    Copy of 1970 Company-Union labor agreement.
  - BPG - MFG - Minutes, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    Minutes of Company-Union meeting re subcontracting labor
  - Cleaning - Grievances and Reports, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    Grievance reports from Cleaning Section
  - Chicago - Contracts, 1970-1973 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    Labor agreement between Company and Union for Chicago Regional Distribution Center located at Des Plaines [11/2/70].
  - Dallas - Contracts, 1971-1974 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    Labor agreement between Company and Union for Dallas Regional Distribution Center located at Arlington [3/25/71].
  - Discipline, Suspension, Discharge, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Georgia - Contracts, 1971-1974 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    Copies of labor agreements made between Company and Union for Georgia RDC at Atlanta [2/18/71 and 3/19/71].
  - H - Grievances and Reports, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    Grievance reports from Henrietta Plant.
  - Irvine - Grievances and Reports, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 28-29)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re routine business.
  - Los Angeles - Contract, 1971-1973 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    Company-Union labor agreement for Los Angeles RDC at Santa Ana [3/31/71].
  - MA - Grievances and Reports, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 31-36)
  - MC - Grievances and Reports, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - MD - Grievances and Reports, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    Grievance reports from Distribution.
  - MF - Grievances and Reports, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 39-43)
  - MH - Grievances and Reports, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - MMS - Grievances and Reports, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - MW (Webster) - Grievances and Reports, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 46)
    Grievance reports from Webster Plant
  - P - Grievances and Reports - Grievances and Reports, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - St. Louis - Contracts, 1971-1974 (Box 35, Folder 48)
    Labor agreement between Company and Union for St. Louis RDC located at Maryland Heights, MO [5/10/71].
  - S - Grievances and Reports, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Washington, DC - Contracts, 1971-1973 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    Labor agreement between Company and Union for Washington RDC at Springfield, VA [7/2/71].
  - X - Grievances, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Discipline, Suspension, Discharge, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 52-53)
    Minutes of Company-Union proceedings re discipline of employees
  - Irvine - Grievances and Reports, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 54)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re plans for first meeting of 1973 contract negotiations and routine business
  - ITG (Information Technology Group) - Grievances and Reports - I, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 55-59)
    Grievance reports from Rochester plants.
  - ITG- Grievances and Reports - II, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 60-65)
  - Contract, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 1-50)
    Includes outline of negotiating committees, Company proposals, Union demands, analyses of economic and Union demands, analyses of Company proposals, agreements reached, copy of final draft (with notes), and copies of final printed draft of 1973-1974 labor agreement.
  - Contracts, 1964-1970 (Box 36, Folder 51)
    Copies of 1964-67 Company union labor agreement, 1967-70 contract, Articles of Contract for Irvine Plant, 1969-72 agreement between Cheshire, Inc. and IAMAW (International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers), and The Xerox World [9/22/67].
  - Contracts, 1970-1973 (Box 36, Folder 52-57)
    Index of labor agreements [6/20/74], copies of 1970 Xerox Corp. contract, memo from MFN re Xerox 1970 Collective Bargaining settlement [3/25/70], copies of 1970-73 articles of contracts for Irvine and Oak Brook Plants, labor agreements for Dallas, Washington, Atlanta, Los Angeles, Atlanta (earlier draft), Chicago, New York, and Cleveland Regional Distribution Centers
  - Contract - I, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 58-60)
    Index of 1973 labor agreements [6/20/74], copy of The Digest with article re new promotion and transfer system in Manufacturing Seniority Unit [10/26/73], copy of 1973-74 Company-Union contract, memo from William Asher to James O'Neill re key elements of 1973 labor negotiations [4/27/73], planning conferences for 1973 negotiations [11/5/71], planning schedule of 1973 contract negotiations [1/12/72], Business Products Group analysis of 1973 contract negotiations [rec'd 3/10/72], statement of collective bargaining agreement objectives [1/73], Company proposals for 1973 contract negotiations, memo from Thomas A. McKibben and Gabriel P. Sparagana to Donald D. Lennox re effects of proposed operating plan [3/14/73], cost of Union economic demand [2/13/73], economic data for 1973 contract negotiations.
  - Contract - II, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 61-67)
    Index of negotiation files [6/20/74], subject index of 1973 contract negotiations [3/20/73 and 4/24/73], memo from J.R. Mullen to Company Negotiating Committee re notable quotes from 1973 contract negotiations [4/30/73], minutes of Company-Union contract negotiation meetings [held from 1/26/73 to 3/18/73].
  - Contract - III, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 1-8)
    Index of negotiation files [6/20/74], minutes of Company-Union contract negotiation meetings (cont'd) [held from 3/21/73 to 4/23/73], revised analysis of Severance Pay Plan, finished product of Severance Pay Plan, Memorandum of Understanding of agreements reached during 1973 negotiations [2/21/73], final draft of Supplemental Agreement A, amendments to earlier Memorandum of Understanding [4/17/73], memorandum of understanding extending and amending 1970 labor agreement between Xerox and ACWA [3/26/73].
  - Discipline, Suspension, Discharge - I, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 9-15)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re employee discipline [1/2/74 to 5/7/74].
  - Discipline, Suspension, Discharge - II, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 16-22)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re employee discipline [5/10/74 to 9/30/74].
  - Discipline, Suspension, Discharge - III, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 23-26)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re employee discipline [10/1/74 to 11/27/74].
  - Irvine, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    Minutes of disciplinary hearings held at Irvine Plant and of Company-Union meeting re routine business
  - ITG - Grievances and Reports - I, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 28-35)
    Grievance reports from Information Technology Group
  - ITG - Grievances and Reports - II, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 36-42)
  - ITG - Grievances and Reports - III, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 43-48)
  - Labor Report - I, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 49-58)
    Labor reports for employee rule violations, dated from 7/74 to 12/74 and alphabetized by employee name in reverse from Z to L.
  - Labor Report - II, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 59-69)
    Labor reports of employee rule violations, dated from 7/74 to 12/74 and alphabetized by employee name in reverse from K to A.
  - Labor Report - III, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 1-6)
    Labor reports of employee rule violations from 6/74.
  - Labor Report - IV, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 7-11)
    Labor reports of employee rule violations from 5/74.
  - Labor Report - V, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 12-17)
    Labor reports of employee rule violations from 4/74.
  - Labor Report - VI, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 18-24)
    Labor reports of employee rule violations from 3/74.
  - Labor Report - VII, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 25-30)
    Labor reports of employee rule violations from 2/74.
  - Labor Report - VIII, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 31-35)
    Labor reports of employee rule violations from 1/74.
  - Oak Brook, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    Minutes of disciplinary hearings at Oak Brook Plant
  - Arbitration - ITG 73-74 - Bearing, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    Company brief outlining position on Bearing arbitration case (ITG 73-74 refers to grievance report number).
  - Arbitration - ITG 74-46 (Henrietta) - LoBello, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 38-40)
    Opinion and award of arbiter, Company brief and Company and Union evidence for LoBello arbitration case (ITG 74-46 refers to grievance report number).
  - Arbitration - ITG 74-101 - Bead Board Case, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 41-44)
    Arbiter's opinion and award, Company brief and evidence submitted by Company and Union (ITG 74-101 refers to grievance number).
  - Arbitration - ISG 75-13 - Tool Room Case, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 45-47)
    Opinion and award of arbiter, Company brief and evidence, Union evidence (ISG 75-13 refers to grievance number).
  - Arbitration - MA 72-54 - Corotron, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 48-50)
    Opinion and award of arbiter, Company brief, Company and Union evidence (MA 72-54 is the grievance report number).
  - Discipline, Suspension, Discharge - I, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 51-56)
    Memos re disciplinary hearings of employees from January to July, 1975.
  - Discipline, Suspension, Discharge - II, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 57-61)
    Disciplinary hearings held from August to December, 1975.
  - ITG & ISG (Information Systems Group) - Grievances and Reports - I, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 62-69)
    Grievance reports from Information Techonology Group and Information Systems Group.
  - ITG & ISG - Grievances and Reports - II, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 70-79)
    Grievance reports from ITG and ISG
  - ITG & ISG - Grievances and Reports - III, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 80-85)
  - Labor Report - I, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 1-12)
    Labor reports of employee rule violations, arranged chronologically.
  - Labor Report - II, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 13-21)
    Labor reports of employee rule violations.
  - Labor Report - III, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 22-24)
  - Arbitration Cases, Pending, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    Memo from William Asher to Leslie Calder re Company's refusal to arbitrate four grievances C2/24/76], copies of materials relating to these cases.
  - Arbitration - ISG 75-221 - Yannatone, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 26-36)
    Arbitration report, Company brief, exhibits, and citations
  - Discipline, Suspension, Discharge - I, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 37-41)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re employee discipline.
  - Discipline, Suspension, Discharge - II, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 42-46)
    Minutes of Company-Union meetings re employee discipline
  - ISG - Grievances and Reports - I, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 47-53)
    Grievance reports from Information Systems Group
  - ISG - Grievances and Reports - II, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 54-60)